[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A plaster cast of a reclining Bigfoot was taken in September of 2000. What is the cast called?", "correct_answer": "The Skookum Cast", "incorrect_answers": ["The Mud Mark", "The Sasquatch Impression", "The Greenville Ape Wallow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which EU member was the largest country in Europe in XIV century, but now has land area of just 65 000 sq. km?", "correct_answer": "Lithuania", "incorrect_answers": ["Denmark", "Austria", "Netherlands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first examples of early Byzantine architecture, found in Ravenna and Constantinople, date from the reign of which Byzantine emperor?", "correct_answer": "Justinian I", "incorrect_answers": ["Justin II", "Tiberius II", "Haraclius"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The smallest dinosaur known to science was the size of a chicken.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these mushrooms is a wild form of the Enokitake mushroom, used in Asian cuisines?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Winter mushrooms", "Velvet foot", "Velvet stem"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish this old phrase:\nWhen you call a dog, he comes right over to you. When you call a cat, she________________.", "correct_answer": "takes a message", "incorrect_answers": ["climbs the curtains", "thinks its dinner time", "runs away from you"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the cartoon Dinosaucers, Bronto Thunder is what kind of dinosaur?", "correct_answer": "An evolved Apatosaurus", "incorrect_answers": ["An evolved Stegosaurus", "An evolved Archaeopteryx", "An evolved Triceratops"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This military complex in North Carolina is one of the largest in the world and home to the 82 Airborne, the Golden Knights, and U.S. Army Special Operations Command.", "correct_answer": "Fort Bragg", "incorrect_answers": ["Fort Campbell", "Fort Polk", "Fort Dix"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries has the highest infant mortality rate according to a 2006 revision of the UN World Population Prospects report?", "correct_answer": "United States", "incorrect_answers": ["Singapore", "Czech Republic", "Sweden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many teams in the National Football League (NFL) are named for animals?", "correct_answer": "14", "incorrect_answers": ["16", "12", "9"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robin Williams provided the voice of Jafar in the animated feature Aladdin.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What artist plays a fortune teller in the movie Carmen: A Hip Hopera?", "correct_answer": "Wyclef Jean", "incorrect_answers": ["Da Brat", "Jermaine Dupri", "Missy Elliott"]}]